Guide to the R.C. Maxwell Company Records, 1891-2001 and undated RL.01071
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Ledgers and Account Books, 1901-1952, 51 boxes
  - Trenton Advertising Company
    - Account binder 9--Folder 5 of 7 (cash received/accounts payable record/personal accounts record), 1913 Nov.-1914 Jan. (Box LA14)
    - Account binder 9--Folder 6 of 7 (sales record/cash received), 1914 Jan.-Dec. (Box LA15)
    - Account binder 9--Folder 7 of 7 (check register/cash received), Jan. 1914-Aug. (Box LA15)
    - Stock shares certificates book, undated (Box LA15)
  - Trenton Poster Advertising Co.
    - Accounts and expenses, 1924-1925 (Box LA16)
    - Accounts by company, 1929-32 (Box LA17)
    - Receipts and disbursements, 1924-1925 (Box LA18)
    - Receipts and disbursements, 1918-1922 (Box LA18)
    - Trial balances monthly, 1918-1923 (Box LA19)
  - Trenton Poster Advertising Co. and Trenton Outdoor Advertising Co.
    - Sales, Trenton Poster Advertising Co. and Trenton Outdoor Advertising Co., 1930 (Box LA20)
  - Trenton Theatre Buildings Company
    - Ledger, 1931 (Box LA21)
  - Unidentified for Company
    - Accounts, 1901-1903 (Box LA22)
    - Accounts, 1911-1914 (Box LA22)
    - Accounts, 1914 (Box LA23)
    - Accounts, 1915-1916 (Box LA23)
    - Accounts, 1917 (Box LA23)
    - Accounts, 1920-1922 (Box LA24)
    - Accounts, 1923-1924 (Box LA24)
    - Accounts--Expenses, 1904-1905 (Box LA25)
    - Accounts--Expenses Trenton, NJ, 1904-1905 (Box LA25)
    - Accounts--Expenses, 1921-1923 (Box LA25)
    - Accounts--Expenses, 1924 (Box LA26)
    - Accounts (National Trial balance), 1920-1924 (Box LA26)
    - Annual lease rental, 1920-1946 (Box LA27)
    - Bank a/c statements, 1943-1952 (Box LA27)
    - Cash account book (Box LA27)
    - Cash and record of client expenses, 1908-1909 (Box LA28)
    - Cash clients balances, 1906-1908 (Box LA29)
    - Cash expenses and credits, 1910 (Box LA30)
    - Company expenses, 1902-1905 (Box LA31)
    - Company expenses, 1906-1908 (Box LA31)
    - Company material/supply expenses, 1916-1918 (Box LA32)
    - Debits and credits operating, 1915-1921 (Box LA33)
    - Expenses, 1901-1904 (Box LA34)
    - Expenses, 1920-21 (Box LA34)
    - Expenses for materials, 1918-1920 (Box LA35)
    - Expenses, including materials used per client and job journal re: particular jobs per month, 1914-1916 (Box LA35)
    - Itemized expenses: cash and credit, 1908-1909 (Box LA36)
    - Ledger, 1907 (Box LA36)
    - Ledger, 1911 (Box LA37)
    - Ledger, 1912 (Box LA37)
    - Ledger, 1913 (Box LA37)
    - Ledger, 1917-1918 (Box LA38)
    - Ledger, 1921-1932 (Box LA39)
    - Ledger, 1929-1931 (Box LA40)
    - Ledger, 1922-1923 (Box LA40)
    - Ledger, 1923-1924 (Box LA41)
    - Ledger, 1924-1925 (Box LA41)
    - Ledger, 1925-1928 (Box LA41)
    - Ledger, 1928-1929 (Box LA41)
    - Ledger, 1929-1934 (Box LA42)
    - Ledger, 1930-1934 (Box LA42)
    - Ledger, 1935-1936 (Box LA42)
    - Ledger, 1935-1944 (Box LA42)
    - Ledger, 1937-1938 (Box LA43)
    - Ledger, 1939-1940 (Box LA43)
    - Ledger, 1941-1942 (Box LA43)
    - Ledger, 1943-1944 (Box LA43)
    - Ledger, 1945-1946 (Box LA44)
    - Ledger, 1945-1952 (Box LA44)
    - Ledger, 1947-1948 (Box LA44)
    - Ledger, 1949 (Box LA44)
    - Long distance telephone calls, 1928-1931 (Box LA45)
    - Miscellaneous accounts, 1931-1932 (Box LA45)
    - Payroll, 1920-1921 (Box LA46)
    - Receipt book (#6), 1946 Jan.-July (Box LA47)
    - Receipt book (#7), 1946 July-1947 Jan. (Box LA47)
    - Receipt book (#8), 1947 Jan.-1947 July (Box LA47)
    - Receipt book (#9), 1947 July-Nov. (Box LA47)
    - Receipt book (#10), 1947 Nov.-1948 May (Box LA47)
    - Receipt book (#11), 1948 May-Sept. (Box LA47)
    - Receipt book (#12), 1948 Sept.-1949 Mar. (Box LA47)
    - Receipt book (#13), 1949 Mar.-Aug. (Box LA47)
    - Receipt book (#14), 1949 Aug.-1950 Feb. (Box LA47)
    - Receipts/Disbursements, 1909-1910 (Box LA48)
    - Sales and expenses, 1916-1917 (Box LA49)
    - Sales and expenses, 1916-1917 (Box LA49)
    - Sales and expenses, 1918-1919 (Box LA49)
    - Sales income and expenses, 1920-1921 (Box LA49)
    - Supplies in shop, 1914-1916 (Box LA50)
    - Trenton, N.J. expenses, 1906-1908 (Box LA51)
- Scrapbooks and Photograph Albums, 1900-1948, 11 boxes
  Contains pictures of advertisements for Coca-Cola with a short description of where they are located. A table of contents in the beginning lists the pages of the pictures by city.
  - Coca-Cola
    - Coca-Cola Pictures, 1927 (Box SC1)
      [Contains pictures of advertisements for Coca-Cola with a short description of where they are located. A table of contents in the beginning lists the pages of the pictures by city.]
    - Coca-Cola 1930, 1930 (Box SC2)
      [Contains pictures of advertisements for Coca-Cola with a short description of the city and the address of where they are located.]
  - D.L. Clark/Clark Brothers Advertising
    - "Scrapbook", c. 1900-1914 (Box SC3)
      [Various pictures of advertisements and photographs of people as well as business cards and other documents attached to it. Some of these have become loose in the scrapbook. Some billboards signed Clark Brothers Adv. Factors, High Point, N.C.]
    - Scrapbook, 1911-1914 (Box SC3)
      [Contains pictures of people, some with descriptions of who they are and the location of the picture.]
  - R.C. Maxwell
    - Scrapbook "Snap-Shots", 1910s (Box SC3)
      [Contains mainly pictures of Coca-Cola advertisements with the location of each picture written on it with the year it was taken.]
    - Scrapbook, 1914-1916 (Box SC4)
      [Contains newspaper advertisements by the R.C. Maxwell Co., Trenton, N.J.]
    - Scrapbook "Photographs", c. 1917 (Box SC5)
      [Contains pictures of Food Conservation advertisements, some with the location of the picture with them.]
    - Geo W. Kleiser Scrapbook (3 folders), 1918 (Box SC6)
      [Photographs of Food Conservation bulletins as well as a letter to Herbert Hoover to install the billboards and several photographs of advertisements for Liberty Bonds.]
    - Herbert C. Hoover photo album (3 folders), 1917 (Box SC6)
      [Photographs of Food Conservation advertisements with their locations and a description/short note out of Herbert C. Hoover's personal scrapbook as well as a letter to Herbert Hoover to install the billboards and several photographs of advertisements to buy Liberty Bonds.]
    - Photo Album 1917: Photographs of Food Conservation Advertising, 1917 (Box SC6)
    - Photo Album (4 folders), circa 1917-1918 (Box SC7)
      [Contains pictures of billboards for Food Conservation, Fuel and Coal Conservation, and Liberty Bonds]
    - Scrapbook, 1920-1928 (Box SC8)
      [Contains various advertisements, pictures, cards, and other documents made for and by the R.C. Maxwell advertising company.]
    - Various billboards, 1920s-1931 (Box SC9)
      [Contains pictures of advertisements for Pillbury Flour, King Midas Flour, Mavis, Purol Gasoline, Tiolene Oil, and Coca-Cola. The pictures are labeled with the location of the advertisement. This scrapbook also contains a smaller scrapbook inside of it with similar contents.]
    - Scrapbook (mainly Coca-Cola), 1920s-1931 (Box SC10)
      [Contains pictures of advertisements for Coca-Cola with the address of where they are located.]
    - Scrapbook (4 folders), 1945-1948 (Box SC11)
      [Contains different newspaper advertisements in TIDE: The Newsmagazing of Advertising, Marketing, and Public Relations.]
- Photographs Included in the ROAD (Resource of Outdoor Advertising Descriptions) Database, 1916-1952 and undated, 79 boxes
  Boxes DB1-DB3 contain prints made from glass negatives. Many are undated, but are grouped together at the beginning of the series because of their format.
  The contents of Boxes DB4-DB6 are arranged according to the numbering systems used by the Maxwell Company between 1916-1920. Maxwell used several different methods for cataloging their photograph collection until around 1918, when the company settled on a single, sequential numbering system. The photographs numbered in this fashion begin in Box DB7. There is thus a chronological overlap among the material in Boxes DB5-DB9. All Maxwell Company numbers are listed immediately under the date of the photographs contained in the box.
  In addition to the Maxwell Company number, items in the Photographs Included in the ROAD Database Series have been assigned ROAD database numbers. A database number beginning with an XXG prefix denotes images made from glass negatives; XXH denotes images primarily from the 1940s (World War II era) but also include a few items in the 1930s; and all other Maxwell images in the ROAD database begin with an XXX prefix. All ROAD database numbers are listed after the Maxwell numbers under each box number. The XXH numbers are out of database order, but are in chronological order. This reflects the fact that this set of photographs was processed separately under a slightly different organizational plan.
  Where applicable, individual folders have been stamped indicating that a corresponding negative is available in the Negatives Series (Restricted) of this collection.
  - Prints from glass negatives, [circa 1916], 124 folders (Box DB1)
    - Maxwell A4-A90, (8-1672)-(8-1682), (4-16)-(145-16) (Box DB1)
    - ROAD XXG001-XXG124 (Box DB1)
  - Prints from glass negatives, 1917-1918, 108 folders (Box DB2)
    - Maxwell (2-17)-(193-17), 8-181[73-18] (Box DB2)
    - ROAD XXG125-XXG232 (Box DB2)
  - Prints from glass negatives, 1918-1919, 117 folders (Box DB3)
    - Maxwell 184-305A, 921-936 (Box DB3)
    - ROAD XXG233-XXG349 (Box DB3)
  - 1916-1917 and undated, 106 folders (Box DB4)
    - Maxwell Unnumbered, A3-A54, [4-16]-[50-17] (Box DB4)
    - ROAD XXX0001-XXX0019, XXX0120-0206 (Box DB4)
  - 1917-1919 and undated, 65 folders (Box DB5)
    - Maxwell [77-17]-[171-17], [8-608]-[8-961] (Box DB5)
    - ROAD XXX0020-0031, XXX0035-0036, XXX0042-0043, XXX0050-0051, XXX0059-0060, XXX0070, XXX0072, XXX0082-0084, XXX0091-0093, XXX0113-0119, XXX0207-0230 (Box DB5)
  - 1918-1920, 87 folders (Box DB6)
    - Maxwell [8-1002]-[8-1238], 22-198 (Box DB6)
    - ROAD XXX0032-0034, XXX0037-0041, XXX0044-0059, XXX0052-0058, XXX0061-0069, XXX0071, XXX0073-0081, XXX0085-0090, XXX0094-0112, XXX0231-XXX0252 (Box DB6)
  - 1918, 84 folders (Box DB7)
    - Maxwell 201-506; 609-855 (Box DB7)
    - ROAD XXX0253-XXX0337 (Box DB7)
  - 1919 Nov.-1920 Apr., 76 folders (Box DB8)
    - Maxwell 858-1004 (Box DB8)
    - ROAD XXX0337[x]-XXX0407 (Box DB8)
  - 1920 Apr.-1920 Aug., 81 folders (Box DB9)
    - Maxwell 1005-1181 (Box DB9)
    - ROAD XXX0408-XXX0488 (Box DB9)
  - 1920 Aug.-1920 Dec., 72 folders (Box DB10)
    - Maxwell [8-]1206-1338 (Box DB10)
    - ROAD XXX0494-XXX0560 (Box DB10)
  - 1920 Dec.-1921 Mar., 79 folders (Box DB11)
    - Maxwell 1341-1528 (Box DB11)
    - ROAD XXX0561-XXX0639 (Box DB11)
  - 1921 Mar.-1921 July, 74 folders (Box DB12)
    - Maxwell 1529-1613 (Box DB12)
    - ROAD XXX0640-XXX0713 (Box DB12)
  - 1921 July-1921 Nov., 77 folders (Box DB13)
    - Maxwell 1614-1702b (Box DB13)
    - ROAD XXX0714-XXX0790 (Box DB13)
  - 1921 Dec.-1922 Mar., 71 folders (Box DB14)
    - Maxwell 1705-1782 (Box DB14)
    - ROAD XXX0791-XXX0861 (Box DB14)
  - 1922 Mar.-1922 May, 69 folders (Box DB15)
    - Maxwell 1783-1850a (Box DB15)
    - ROAD XXX0862-XXX0930 (Box DB15)
  - 1922 May-1922 July, 88 folders (Box DB16)
    - Maxwell 1850b-1885 (Box DB16)
    - ROAD XXX0931-XXX1018 (Box DB16)
  - 1922 July-1923 Jan., 84 folders (Box DB17)
    - Maxwell 1886-1960a-d (Box DB17)
    - ROAD XXX1019-XXX1102 (Box DB17)
  - 1923 Jan.-1923 Apr., 72 folders (Box DB18)
    - Maxwell 1961-2034 (Box DB18)
    - ROAD XXX1103-XXX1174 (Box DB18)
  - 1923 Apr.-1924 Sept., 77 folders (Box DB19)
    - Maxwell 2035-2159 (Box DB19)
    - ROAD XXX1175-XXX1252 (Box DB19)
  - 1924 Sept.-1925 Mar., 67 folders (Box DB20)
    - Maxwell 2166-2239a(-9) (Box DB20)
    - ROAD XXX1253-XXX1320 (Box DB20)
  - 1925 Apr.-1925 Aug., 74 folders (Box DB21)
    - Maxwell 2240-2319 (Box DB21)
    - ROAD XXX1321-XXX1395 (Box DB21)
  - 1925 Aug.-1926 May, 88 folders (Box DB22)
    - Maxwell 2320-2388 (Box DB22)
    - ROAD XXX1396-XXX1483 (Box DB22)
  - 1926 May-1927 July, 90 folders (Box DB23)
    - Maxwell 2390-2489 (Box DB23)
    - ROAD XXX1484-XXX1562 and XXX3075 (Box DB23)
  - 1927 July-1928 Apr., 85 folders (Box DB24)
    - Maxwell 2490-2565b (Box DB24)
    - ROAD XXX1573-XXX1675 (Box DB24)
  - 1928 May-1929 Mar., 88 folders (Box DB25)
    - Maxwell 2566-2650a (Box DB25)
    - ROAD XXX1658-XXX1745 (Box DB25)
  - 1929 Mar.-1930 Sept.?, 103 folders (Box DB26)
    - Maxwell 2651-2755h (Box DB26)
    - ROAD XXX1746-XXX1849 (Box DB26)
  - 1930 Sept.-1932 Feb., 100 folders (Box DB27)
    - Maxwell 2755i-2859a (Box DB27)
    - ROAD XXX1850-XXX1949 (Box DB27)
  - 1932 Feb.-1933 Feb., 106 folders (Box DB28)
    - Maxwell 2859b-2942b (Box DB28)
    - ROAD XXX1950-XXX2055 (Box DB28)
  - 1923 Oct.-1934 May, 112 folders (Box DB29)
    - Maxwell 2942c-3022f (Box DB29)
    - ROAD XXX2056-XXX2167 (Box DB29)
  - 1923 Oct.-1924 Apr., 102 folders (Box DB30)
    - Maxwell 3022g-3121 (Box DB30)
    - ROAD XXX2168-XXX2270 (Box DB30)
  - 1924 Apr.-1934 May, 105 folders (Box DB31)
    - Maxwell 3122-3185 (Box DB31)
    - ROAD XXX2271-XXX2375 (Box DB31)
  - 1931-1950, 115 folders (Box DB32)
    - Maxwell [unnumbered] (Box DB32)
    - ROAD XXH2660-XXH2927 (Box DB32)
  - 1934 Apr.-1934 Sept., 109 folders (Box DB33)
    - Maxwell 3186-3288 (Box DB33)
    - ROAD XXX2376-XXX2484 (Box DB33)
  - 1934 Oct.-1935 Feb., 101 folders (Box DB34)
    - Maxwell 3289-3388 (Box DB34)
    - ROAD XXX2485-XXX2585 (Box DB34)
  - 1934 Feb.-1935 Apr., 100 folders (Box DB35)
    - Maxwell 3389-3503 (Box DB35)
    - ROAD XXX2586-XXX2685 (Box DB35)
  - 1935 Apr.-1935 June, 98 folders (Box DB36)
    - Maxwell 3504-3610 (Box DB36)
    - ROAD XXX2686-XXX2783 (Box DB36)
  - 1935 June-1935 Sept., 98 folders (Box DB37)
    - Maxwell 3611-3718 (Box DB37)
    - ROAD XXX2784-XXX2881 (Box DB37)
  - 1935 Sept.-1936 Feb., 106 folders (Box DB38)
    - Maxwell 3719-3811a (Box DB38)
    - ROAD XXX2882-XXX2987 (Box DB38)
  - 1936 Feb.-1937 Oct., 96 folders (Box DB39)
    - Maxwell 3812-3914a (Box DB39)
    - ROAD XXX2988-XXX3805 (Box DB39)
  - 1936 May-1937 Oct., 104 folders (Box DB40)
    - Maxwell 3914b-4021 (Box DB40)
    - ROAD XXX3086-XXX3188 (Box DB40)
  - 1936 June-1936 Aug, 102 folders (Box DB41)
    - Maxwell 4022-4135 (Box DB41)
    - ROAD XXX3189-XXX3290 (Box DB41)
  - 1936 Aug.-1936 Oct., 98 folders (Box DB42)
    - Maxwell 4137-4219k (Box DB42)
    - ROAD XXX3291-XXX3388 (Box DB42)
  - 1936 Oct.-1937 Jan., 107 folders (Box DB43)
    - Maxwell 4219L-4317 (Box DB43)
    - ROAD XXX3389-XXX3495 (Box DB43)
  - 1937 Jan.-1937 Mar., 104 folders (Box DB44)
    - Maxwell 4318-4420 (Box DB44)
    - ROAD XXX3496-XXX3544; XXX3693-3747 (Box DB44)
      For items XXX3545-XXX3615, please see box DB45.
      For items XXX3616-XXX3692, please see box DB46.
  - 1937 Mar.-1937 May, 97 folders (Box DB45)
    - Maxwell 4421-4510 (Box DB45)
    - ROAD XXX3748-XXX3773; XXX3545-XXX3615 (Box DB45)
  - 1937 May-1937 July, 105 folders (Box DB46)
    - Maxwell 4511-4618 (Box DB46)
    - ROAD XXX3616-XXX3692; XXX3774-XXX3801 (Box DB46)
  - 1937 July-1937 Sept., 105 folders (Box DB47)
    - Maxwell 4620-4731 (Box DB47)
    - ROAD XXX3802-XXX3906 (Box DB47)
  - 1937 Sept.-1937 Dec., 103 folders (Box DB48)
    - Maxwell 4732-4837 (Box DB48)
    - ROAD XXX3907-XXX4009 (Box DB48)
  - 1937 Dec.-1938 Apr., 102 folders (Box DB49)
    - Maxwell 4838-4962 (Box DB49)
    - ROAD XXX4010-XXX4111 (Box DB49)
  - 1938 Apr.-1938 June, 107 folders (Box DB50)
    - Maxwell 4963-5078a (Box DB50)
    - ROAD XXX4112-XXX4218 (Box DB50)
  - 1938 June-1938 Aug., 102 folders (Box DB51)
    - Maxwell 5079-5239 (Box DB51)
    - ROAD XXX4219-XXX4320 (Box DB51)
  - 1938 Aug.-1938 Dec., 98 folders (Box DB52)
    - Maxwell 5240-5359 (Box DB52)
    - ROAD XXX4321-XXX4418 (Box DB52)
  - 1938 Dec.-1939 Apr., 107 folders (Box DB53)
    - Maxwell 5360-5461 (Box DB53)
    - ROAD XXX4419-XXX4525 (Box DB53)
  - 1939 Apr.-1939 June, 106 folders (Box DB54)
    - Maxwell 5462-5588 (Box DB54)
    - ROAD XXX4526-XXX4631 (Box DB54)
  - 1939 June-1939 July, 107 folders (Box DB55)
    - Maxwell 5589-5754a (Box DB55)
    - ROAD XXX4632-XXX4738 (Box DB55)
  - 1939 July-1939 Nov., 106 folders (Box DB56)
    - Maxwell 5755-5874 (Box DB56)
    - ROAD XXX4739-XXX4845 (Box DB56)
  - 1939 Nov.-1949 Sept., 100 folders (Box DB57)
    - Maxwell 5874a-5917; 7505-7506; 7819; 9549; 9551-9656 (Box DB57)
    - ROAD XXX4846-XXX4946 (Box DB57)
  - 1940 Jan. 23-1940 Oct. 17, 119 folders (Box DB58)
    - Maxwell 5508, 5908-6199 (Box DB58)
    - ROAD XXH0280-XXH0552 (Box DB58)
  - 1940 Oct. 21-1941 July 30, 104 folders (Box DB59)
    - Maxwell 6200-6441 (Box DB59)
    - ROAD XXH1185-XXH1277, XXH0850-XXH0984 (Box DB59)
  - 1941 Aug. 5-1942 July 16, 97 folders (Box DB60)
    - Maxwell 6442-6598, 6698-6716 (Box DB60)
    - ROAD XXH0985-XXH1184, XXH0122-XXH0133, XXH3279-XXH3281 (Box DB60)
      Items XXH0001-XXH0121 are duplicated in later XXH numbers, so are not listed in this finding aid. The duplicate numbers are noted in the ROAD database.
  - 1941 Dec. 22-1944, 122 folders (Box DB61)
    - Maxwell 6595-6697 (Box DB61)
    - ROAD XXH2928-XXH3057 (Box DB61)
  - 1944 Sept. 2-1946 Mar. 5, 91 folders (Box DB62)
    - Maxwell 6718-6994, 8656 (Box DB62)
    - ROAD XXH0134-XXH0279, XXH0553-XXH0630, XXH3282-XXH3295 (Box DB62)
      For items XXH0122-XXH0133, please see box DB60.
      For items XXH0280-XXX0552, please see box DB58.
  - 1946 Mar. 5-1946 Sept. 13, 95 folders (Box DB63)
    - Maxwell 6995-6200, 1204-1205, 7212-7286 (Box DB63)
    - ROAD XXH0631-XXH0849, XXH3058-XXH3080 (Box DB63)
      For items XXH0850-XXH0984, please see box DB59.
  - 1946 Sept. 13-1947 Jan. 24, 104 folders (Box DB64)
    - Maxwell 7287-7724 (Box DB64)
    - ROAD XXH3081-XXH3278, XXH1477-XXH1540 (Box DB64)
  - 1947 Jan. 24-1948 June 17, 94 folders (Box DB65)
    - Maxwell 7725-7902, 8448, 8525-8591 (Box DB65)
    - ROAD XXH1541-XXH1698, XXH2602, XXH1278-XXH1343 (Box DB65)
      For items XXH3279-XXH3281, please see box DB60.
      For items XXH1699-XXH1805, please see box DB68.
      For items XXH2537-2659, please see box DB79.
  - 1947 May 22-1947 Oct. 14, 125 folders (Box DB66)
    - Maxwell 7903-8200 (Box DB66)
    - ROAD XXH3550-XXH3827 (Box DB66)
      For items XXH3295-XXH3549, please see box DB67.
  - 1947 Oct. 14-1948 June 2, 122 folders (Box DB67)
    - Maxwell 8201-8519 (Box DB67)
    - ROAD XXH3295-XXH3549 (Box DB67)
      For items XXH3550-XXH3827, please see box DB66.
  - 1948 June 17-1948 Aug. 28, 113 folders (Box DB68)
    - Maxwell 8593-8856 (Box DB68)
    - ROAD XXH1344-XXH1476, XXH1699-XXH1805 (Box DB68)
      For items XXH1477-XXH1540, please see box DB64.
      For items XXH1541-XXH1698, please see box DB65.
  - 1948 Aug. 28-1949 Feb. 15, 106 folders (Box DB69)
    - Maxwell 8857-9130 (Box DB69)
    - ROAD XXH1806-XXH2064 (Box DB69)
  - 1949 Feb. 19-1949 June 4, 103 folders (Box DB70)
    - Maxwell 9131-9401 (Box DB70)
    - ROAD XXH2065-XXH2298 (Box DB70)
  - 1949 June 16-1952 Sept. 10, 104 folders (Box DB71)
    - Maxwell 9402-9542, 10414-11789 (Box DB71)
    - ROAD XXH2299-XXH2536 (Box DB71)
      For items XXH2537-XXH2659, please see box DB779.
      For item XXH2602, please see box DB65.
  - 1949 Sept.-1950 Feb., 108 folders (Box DB72)
    - Maxwell 9657-9773 (Box DB72)
    - ROAD XXX4947-XXX5054 (Box DB72)
  - 1950 Feb.-1950 Apr., 100 folders (Box DB73)
    - Maxwell 9778-9901 (Box DB73)
    - XXX5055-XXX5154 (Box DB73)
  - 1950 Apr.-1950 June, 97 folders (Box DB74)
    - Maxwell 9902-10019 (Box DB74)
    - ROAD XXX5155-XXX5240 (Box DB74)
  - 1950 June-1950 July, 93 folders (Box DB75)
    - Maxwell 10020-10130 (Box DB75)
    - ROAD XXX5241-XXX5318, XXX5359-XXX5377 (Box DB75)
      For items XXX5319-XXX5358, please see box DB76.
  - 1950 July-1950 Oct., 101 folders (Box DB76)
    - Maxwell 100131-10256 (Box DB76)
    - ROAD XXX5378-XXX5398, XXX5319-XXX5358, XXX5400-XXX5439 (Box DB76)
  - 1950 Oct.-1951 Feb., 108 folders (Box DB77)
    - Maxwell 10258-10421 (Box DB77)
    - ROAD XXX5440-XXX5547 (Box DB77)
  - 1951 Feb.-1951 Mar., 75 folders (Box DB78)
    - Maxwell 10422-10538 (Box DB78)
    - ROAD XXX5548-XXX5622 (Box DB78)
  - 1952 Sept. 10-1952 Dec. 1, 56 folders, box is not full (Box DB79)
    - Maxwell 11790-11925 (Box DB79)
    - ROAD XXH2537-XXH2659 (Box DB79)
- Photographs NOT Included in the ROAD Database, 1951-1991 and undated, 100 boxes
  Items in this series have not been included in the ROAD database. There is a slight overlap in dates (1951-1952) with items in the Photographs Included in the ROAD Database Series; however, there is no overlap in actual items between the two series. Photographs are listed in chronological order and according to the Maxwell numbering system.
  - 1951 Mar.-1951 June, 98 folders (Box NP1)
    - Maxwell 10539-10689 (Box NP1)
  - 1951 June-1951 Aug., 104 folders (Box NP2)
    - Maxwell 10690-10851 (Box NP2)
  - 1951 Aug., 90 folders (Box NP3)
    - Maxwell 10852-10962 (Box NP3)
  - 1951 Sept.-1951 Oct., 105 folders (Box NP4)
    - Maxwell 10982-11093 (Box NP4)
  - 1953 Jan.-1953 Apr., 85 folders (Box NP5)
    - Maxwell 11999-12119 (Box NP5)
  - 1953 Apr.-1953 June, 93 folders (Box NP6)
    - Maxwell 12120-12233 (Box NP6)
  - 1953 June, 26 folders (Box NP7)
    - Maxwell 12234-12269 (Box NP7)
  - 1953 Sept. 4-1953 Sept. 24, 95 folders (Box NP8)
    - Maxwell 12462-12598 (Box NP8)
  - 1953 Sept. 30-1953 Nov. 16, 99 folders (Box NP9)
    - Maxwell 12601-12718 (Box NP9)
  - 1953 Nov. 16-1954 Jan. 4, 101 folders (Box NP10)
    - Maxwell 12719-12856 (Box NP10)
  - 1954 Jan. 8-1954 Apr. 7, 97 folders (Box NP11)
    - Maxwell 12857-12976 (Box NP11)
  - 1954 Apr. 10-1954 May 30, 98 folders (Box NP12)
    - Maxwell 12977-13112 (Box NP12)
  - 1954 May 30-1954 July 13, 99 folders (Box NP13)
    - Maxwell 13113-13239 (Box NP13)
  - 1954 July 13-1954 July 29, 100 folders (Box NP14)
    - Maxwell 13240-13339 (Box NP14)
  - 1954 July 29-1954 Aug. 18, 101 folders (Box NP15)
    - Maxwell 13341-13478 (Box NP15)
  - 1954 Aug. 18-1954 Sept. 6, 101 folders (Box NP16)
    - Maxwell 13479-13593 (Box NP16)
  - 1954 Sept. 6-1954 Sept. 29, 90 folders (Box NP17)
    - Maxwell 13594-13702 (Box NP17)
  - 1954 Nov. 11-1955 Feb. 10, 102 folders (Box NP18)
    - Maxwell 13703-13833 (Box NP18)
  - 1955 Feb. 14-1955 Apr. 11, 99 folders (Box NP19)
    - Maxwell 13834-13990 (Box NP19)
  - 1955 Apr. 15-1955 June 16, 112 folders (Box NP20)
    - Maxwell 13994-14157 (Box NP20)
  - 1955 June 17-1955 July 14, 100 folders (Box NP21)
    - Maxwell 14159-14273 (Box NP21)
  - 1955 July 14-1955 Sept. 4, 107 folders (Box NP22)
    - Maxwell 14274-14410 (Box NP22)
  - 1955 Sept. 4-1955 Oct. 20, 101 folders (Box NP23)
    - Maxwell 14411-14528 (Box NP23)
  - 1955 Oct. 20-1955 Dec. 28, 92 folders (Box NP24)
    - Maxwell 14529-14636 (Box NP24)
  - 1955 Dec. 28-1956 Mar. 15, 96 folders (Box NP25)
    - Maxwell 14637-14754 (Box NP25)
  - 1956 Mar. 15-1956 May 2, 90 folders (Box NP26)
    - Maxwell 14755-14913 (Box NP26)
  - 1956 May 8-1956 June 26, 94 folders (Box NP27)
    - Maxwell 14914-15027 (Box NP27)
  - 1956 June 28-1956 July 17, 91 folders (Box NP28)
    - Maxwell 15029-15161 (Box NP28)
  - 1956 July 17-1956 Aug. 28, 106 folders (Box NP29)
    - Maxwell 15161-15305 (Box NP29)
  - 1956 Aug. 29-1956 Sept. 26, 99 folders (Box NP30)
    - Maxwell 15308(01)-15321 (Box NP30)
  - 1956 Sept. 1-1956 Oct. 19, 83 folders (Box NP31)
    - Maxwell 15322-15464 (Box NP31)
  - 1956 Oct. 19-1956 Dec. 20, 96 folders (Box NP32)
    - Maxwell 15466-15593 (Box NP32)
  - 1956 Dec. 20-1957 Mar. 25, 90 folders (Box NP33)
    - Maxwell 15594-15708 (Box NP33)
  - 1956 Mar.-1957 May 31, 94 folders (Box NP34)